♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
It's such a treat to be
at the water park with you guys.
I don't want to
freak anyone out,
but Meg is just openly weeping
at the touch tank.
[crying] It's been so long.
-Okay. All right.
-I need this so much.
-This is a gift.
-Just gonna...
-You have no idea.
-...move along here.
You're giving me a gift
right now.
You-you take care now.
Yeesh. Imagine being that
desperate for human connection.
Anyway, sir, I've been
stung by a jellyfish,
and I need to be peed on.
Our jellyfish don't sting.
[chuckles] Yeah, I think,
I think I know
when I've been stung.
Now is there an attractive,
well-hydrated manager
I can speak to?
Everyone having fun?
You know, this is
our first family time
since we went to Dollywood.
-Aw.
-What?
It's just not what I thought
the sign would look like.
I mean, it's got two O's
right next to each other,
and, you know, it's just...
missed opportunity.
Where's Stewie?
Hey, Bri, can dolphins sting,
and-and what'll that get me,
pee-wise?
Ah...!
Stewie!
[barking]
Well, I'm out of ideas.
Someone, help! My baby!
Peter, jump in and save him!
On it! Hang on. Hold my phone.
Hold my ear buds.
Hold my second phone
I hide from your mother.
-[phone chimes]
-Hang on.
Respond with an eggplant emoji.
[grunts]
Hey, check out the new addition.
She's hot.
Eh, tank hot.
♪ ♪
[panting]
Meg! You saved Stewie!
Thank God everyone is safe.
And as for you, young lady...
-I guess I'm in trouble, huh?
-No, not at all.
In fact, we have a job opening
over at our waterslide park.
I think you'd make
an excellent lifeguard.
Will you apply for the position?
You mean it?
Wow, I feel like
I'm in a fairy tale.
Now that my sister is dead,
I must have her ruby slippers.
Oh, no.
Those shoes now belong...
to Meg.
♪ ♪
Ah! [bleep]
We're not even close
to the same size!
Get 'em off, get 'em off!
[crying out]
[announcer] In Oz,
there's no place like home.
For big women's shoes,
there's no place like Kohl's.
What software is that?
"Final Draft: 'Extra Visible
To Nearby Patrons
In the Coffeehouse' Edition"?
Just trying to get
a little work done...
on my Hollywood screenplay,
for Hollywood.
Home of
big Hollywood celebrities.
Ike Barinholtz,
being an example.
Do not patronize this man!
I found an insensitive post
in his Twitter feed!
What? I-I would never.
He tweeted something
very negative
about Abbott Elementary.
I-I said it was hilarious.
But you didn't use all caps.
You're canceled, mister.
[all booing]
I'll just gather my things.
[West]
Per hipster law,
when a coffeehouse
becomes available,
it goes to whoever has the best
coffee pun for the name.
Um, Java the Hut.
Perks and Recreation.
Uh, Lost and Ground.
-Roast Malone.
-Two and a Caf Men.
[West]
This can go on
for quite a while.
Why, this very shop started
in the '80s as Funky Brewster,
and then Delta Perk.
In the mid-'90s,
it was briefly a tavern
called Dharma & Grog,
and then...
-[barking]
-Uhp.
I'll send you back now.
Got to get the dog.
Daisy! Daisy!
It's just the barley man.
You know the barley man.
The Unflushed Poo & Tea Leaf.
Bathroom Key Code & Tea Leaf.
The Center
for Homeless Armpit-Washing.
Brian, Brian.
Everyone's gone.
Yup, it's all yours.
You can name it whatever.
Wow, what should we do first?
We should hang
an "Under New Management" banner
to generate interest.
Whoa, someone different
is signing the time cards.
I got to check this place out.
Really glad you're applying
for the lifeguard position, Meg.
I just have a few questions.
"If I were to ask you
how many times a day you shower,
-what would you say?"
-Uh...
The pool is a shower?
Wow, skipping to page two.
Let's see,
this is all just boilerplate
about making sure
to hassle the urban kids
-like they're gonna somehow
steal the pool.
-Right, right, right.
That was in the application
packet you emailed.
Okay, well,
you're basically hired.
The only lifeguard test left is
for you to run all sultry
in slow motion.
["Yakety Sax" playing]
♪ ♪
-[song ends]
-Okay, we can work on that.
Wow, we're finally going
to open our coffeehouse today.
I've been dreaming of this day
for most of the day,
and now it finally pays off.
Yup, only thing left to do is
put the right music on
the Sonos.
[automated voice]
Connecting:
-Brian's Knockoff iPhone.
-Wait, why does it say that?
[automated voice]
Playing: Jazz Music
Brian Never Actually Listens To.
-[jazz music playing]
-Mmm, love this one.
[automated voice] Favorited,
but not listened to once.
Not one single time.
It's okay, Bri, I got this.
[automated voice]
Connecting: Stewie's iPad
That His Mom Has to
Unlock for Him.
Whoa, no, not always.
[automated voice] Playing:
Songs That Are Guys' Names.
[male singer]
♪ Robert! ♪
Stop, stop,
we're overthinking this.
It's a coffeehouse.
We're legally required
-to play Sheryl Crow's
worst songs.
-You're right.
Anyway, what matters is
we're finally ready
to open our new café:
"Oh Joe You D'int."
Uh, did-did we...
did we settle on that name?
[laughs]
Don't ask me.
You're the one
who keeps bringing us back
-to "Oh Joe You D'int."
-Yeah, I don't like that one.
And yet here we are
talking about it.
You're the one
who won't let it go.
Yeah, me,
I'm open to whatever.
All right,
are we serving coffee or what?
[busy chatter]
Welcome, everyone.
Step right up
and get yourself some coffee.
Stewie, hook these people up
with some coffee.
Okay, where did you
put the coffee?
Me? Wha-- I-- you were in charge
of getting the coffee,
I-I was coming up with
"Oh Joe You D'int."
Well, frick.
Okay, okay, make it look
like we can't help anyone
because we're preparing
a giant order for DoorDash.
-How do we do that?
-Just start throwing
a bunch of stuff into bags,
and I'll keep asking
if the next person
through the door is Dave.
Dave? You Dave?
-Dave?
-What about us?
You're actually here,
so you don't matter.
-[lively chatter]
-♪ ♪
[Meg]
A job can be more than a job,
if you love what you do.
I am a lifeguard
because I love flashing
eye-level swimsuit crotch shots
at families.
I love checking
the pH of the pool
by gargling the water and seeing
how quickly it gives me
a yeast infection.
[thud]
Okay, pH a little high here.
I love having a special whistle
that, when you blow it,
it makes the sound of Ray Romano
telling people to cut it out.
[Ray Romano's voice]
All right, guys,
that's enough over there.
[Meg]
But what I love most
about being a lifeguard?
No more abuse from my family.
In fact,
no family at all.
It's just me,
all day, every day.
-[Peter] Hey, Meg!
-Dad?!
Great news.
Since you work here,
I got a discount
on a season pass!
I'll be here all day,
every day.
And don't worry,
I won't set up my towel
next to the breastfeeding moms.
Don't forget to swap halfway
through so you keep 'em even.
Dad, you have no right
to hang out in my workplace.
Well, maybe your workplace
should've thought of that
before they put an ad
on my juice box.
I'm a lifeguard, you know.
I could just throw you out.
Aw, come on, Meg.
Look, if you let me stay,
we'll make one of
those viral videos you love.
You know, where something seems
real, but it's actually cake.
Yo, yo, yo, I'm here
with my daughter, Meg,
and her brother, Chris.
Or am I?
Ow, Dad! Stop it!
Wait, what happened
to Cake Chris?
All right, let's see
what's happening on CakeHub.
[sultry music playing]
What a dirty little cake.
Okay, plus, plus,
you know "laugh and cry"?
You know the-- in the song where
Stewie says "laugh and cry"?
Let me stay, Meg,
and it's all yours.
-You'd do that?
-I will look into it.
I will look into it
very strongly.
[softly]
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
Okay, I guess so.
But only if you promise
to follow all the rules.
Guys, we're in!
-Hey, Meg.
-Hey.
Meg, I saw a sign
about active diarrhea.
What if it's very passive?
[busy chatter]
What are we gonna do, Stewie?!
These people came for coffee,
and we have none to serve them!
Dude, come on.
Can I get some coffee or what?
Uh, hang on. I think I hear
our delivery guy in the back.
What do you mean
you don't have the coffee?!
[as delivery guy]
I-I know, I'm sorry,
and-and for such a handsome guy,
too.
-You're so handsome.
-[as himself] Okay, pal,
you're not gonna compliment
your way out of this one.
[as delivery guy] Ah, geez,
buddy, you look so tense.
Let's get you out of that apron.
[as himself]
Oh, come on, I'm at work.
[as delivery guy] Oh,
when is that body not working?
Sorry, hang on, just got to deal
with this stupid thing.
Enough of this.
Come on, other college students.
Let's go sign up
for a credit card
that gives us a T-shirt!
[indistinct chatter]
Wait! Hang on!
We got coffee for you
right here.
Yep, the highest quality
that you've come to expect
here at "Brew Ha Ha."
I want to change our name
to "Brew Ha Ha."
You're a lifesaver.
Where did you get that?
I ran to the bodega next door
and got some Folgers.
What? We'll never get away
with serving Folgers.
Won't we? Look around,
we're a hit.
[indistinct chatter]
And check it out, we're already
a pretend small business
in a Chase Bank ad.
♪ ♪
[Brian]
These days, running a small
business can be a big challenge.
[Stewie]
Whether we're receiving
a flower delivery
for unclear reasons...
[Brain]
Or raising the blinds
and flipping over
the "Open/Closed" sign,
which is how I spend
most of my work day...
[Stewie]
Or even making a latte
for a Black woman,
an iced tea for a white woman,
and a coffee
for a gently brown guy
who could go in a lot of
different directions...
[Brian]
We've got our hands full.
That's why Chase Bank
is here for us.
[Stewie]
When this man in a suit
from Chase Bank
came down and shook my hand
at my place of business,
it really solidified
what we'd already talked about
at his office.
[Brian]
Now we're looking at a laptop,
like my stupid
little coffee shop
is gonna be a big disruptor
in the online space.
[Stewie]
And my Chase business card
allows me to make those
emergency purchases
that I'll lose sleep
at night over.
[Brian]
Chase understands my business
the way they understand
all businesses,
as a huge reverse funnel
that shoves money
upwards to them.
[Stewie]
Hey, another flower delivery.
These'll look great
in the bathroom,
while I'm pooping blood
from the stress.
[Brian]
Now I'm flipping over that
"Open/Closed" sign again.
Is that a new stadium
with Chase's name on it?
How'd they afford that?
[Stewie]
I'll be in this bathroom
for a while.
Better toss it to the announcer.
[announcer] At Chase Bank,
we're about more than just
foreclosing on American
servicemen while overseas.
We're about small business.
So when you think of Chase,
don't think of
the 2008 financial crash,
think of your local,
sympathetic small business.
Flower delivery.
[Stewie] Yeah, guys, we're good
on flowers for a while.
Well, that's great, but it
doesn't change the fact that
we're passing Folgers off
as real coffee.
Isn't someone going to
know the taste of Folgers?
Relax, Stewie. The only person
who could possibly
know the taste of Folgers
would be an older white man
who works in public education.
I would like
a cup of coffee, please.
Oh...
[studio audience laughs]
[woman speaking Japanese]
[laughing]
Dad, you promised
you'd follow all the rules.
I told you, no horseplay.
[laughs] We're having big
wrassle-fights
a'cause it's the only way we
know how to express affection.
-Gonna get you, Peter.
-Me, too.
And not because I love you
and I don't have the words
to say it.
I'm just having normal fun
without all that mess.
Okay, guys, out of the pool.
I gave you a chance,
and you blew it.
You're kicked out of the park.
-What?
-Go home.
I'm kicking you out.
Gotta catch me first.
Just try to get me out of
the deep end
with these long-legged,
short-torsoed giants.
Dad!
Oh, my God, he's not breathing.
♪ ♪
Okay, guys. Come on now.
Please breathe, Dad.
-Hey.
Your mouth was... on my mouth.
Uh, I think.
Maybe a little. Yeah.
My God, Peter.
That's your daughter.
Adopted daughter?
No, Woody,
just-just regular daughter.
Oh, ye-yeah, then ew,
that's-that's wrong, ew.
♪ ♪
Okay, so... our mouths were...
totally touching each other.
Y-Yes.
But that's okay. That's okay.
'Cause you were saving my life,
so it's not weird.
Right, it's not w--
It's the opposite of weird.
Yeah, the opposite. Right, yeah.
And, anyway, we can just
say this never happened, right?
'Cause nobody even saw us.
[laughing]
Ooh, they're all distracted.
Other urban kids,
this is our chance.
♪ ♪
Stewie, what are we gonna do?
If we serve coffee to
Principal Shepherd,
he's gonna recognize
that it's Folgers.
I say we wait him out.
Any middle-aged white man
can be ignored indefinitely,
unless he clears his throat.
[clears throat]
Welp, we're out of moves.
Um, hi. How may I help you?
I would like a cup of coffee.
Y-Yes, sir. Uh, coming right up.
♪ ♪
Wait a minute, this is
Folgers instant coffee.
[crowd exclaims]
I would know,
we served it at my wedding.
Yes, everyone, we admit it.
We didn't have our normal
coffee beans on hand,
and so we've been
serving you the cheap stuff.
You're all drinking Folgers.
That's awesome.
It... it is?
Heck yeah, man.
We're, like, paying way a lot
of our parents' money
for our parents'
own cheap coffee?
That's kind of meta.
Like, seriously alt and iro.
[crowd murmurs in agreement]
Well, that went different
from how I expected.
Yup, kids these days are
pretty forgiving and tolerant.
This dog and baby are banned
from society forever
'cause of an Internet thing.
One of them keeps trying to
slide into AOC's DMs.
-Brian?
-She's hot,
but we're supposed to
pretend she's not.
Well, who's that
red lipstick for?
[crowd boos]
I guess the coffee shop's
available.
Roast Busters.
Good luck.
♪ ♪
Oh, back from the water park,
you two?
Anything unusual happen?
Yeah. No. I mean,
I did mouth-to-mouth
on this one guy,
but he was, like,
way not blood-related.
Okay. Guess I'll just
watch the news.
Our top story, creepy lip-lock
saves a life
at Quahog water park.
Local man Peter Griffin
was revived by
a game of tonsil-hockey with
lifeguard Meg Griffin,
who-- I'm placing
my hand over my ear
and pretending to
get new information--
is his own daughter?
Babe, it's not what you think.
Yeah, I was just
saving his life.
He means nothing to me.
I want to believe that, Meg.
But look what people
are saying on Facebook.
"This is wrong," Bonnie Swanson.
"So not okay," Donna Brown.
"Russia USA number one support,"
woman's face with
Getty Image watermark.
Our family is a laughing stock.
Why are you being like this?
I was just doing my job.
I know, but I'm sorry,
it-it's just weird.
I feel humiliated.
If you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go
smoke a cigarette alone,
which is how TV depicts
a woman at her
lowest point emotionally.
This is insane.
Yeah, when are people
gonna grow up?
♪ Peter and Megan,
sitting in a tree ♪
♪ K-I-S-S... ♪
Oh...
♪ E... N-G. ♪
-[bell rings]
-[announcer] And Chris Griffin
is eliminated,
which means Boopresh Armiteg
will repeat as
National Spelling Champion.
Congrats to his
always-frowning Indian parents
joylessly clapping
in the audience.
[applause]
♪ ♪
Guys, we called this meeting
because there are a lot of
hurtful rumors swirling around,
-and we have something to
say to you.
-That's right.
-You guys are being stupid.
-Meg and I are in love.
What? No, Dad,
we're telling them that
they're idiots
-and to cut it out.
-Right, I--
That's what I meant,
I-I'm all confused.
I-I'm not in love with Meg,
I-I ju--
I need to
return a ring to Zales.
[crying]
[both gasp]
Oh, my God,
your father's not breathing.
Meg, you have to
give him mouth-to-mouth.
Me? You do it. You're his wife.
I need at least four beers to
get there, Meg.
Besides, you're
the only one who knows how.
No way, I already did it once,
and it made my life hell.
Meg, please. This is our father!
Probably.
What's that supposed to mean?
We've all heard stories of
your time on
the Hoobastank tour bus.
Meg, your father is dying
and he needs you,
and I am not going
to sit here and apologize for
what I may or may not have done
with the Hoobastank bassist.
"Hoobastank bassist"?
You don't even know
the guy's name.
They've had like
five bass players,
and, anyway, it's not
like I was writing down names.
[Peter gasps]
What's the big deal?
You stick your tongue
down Dad's throat.
Most natural thing in the world.
Where the hell have you been?
Brian and I did a coffee house
thing, I don't know.
[cell phone rings]
I have to take this. Hey, you.
Listen, Meg. I'm glad
you saved my life at the pool.
But I'm sorry
I came there in the first place.
Everyone deserves
a place of their own,
and I get that now.
I promise I'll treat you
better in the future.
You know, we've had
conversations like this
again and again,
and nothing ever changes.
You're a terrible father,
and I'm counting the days
till I move out of this house.
Okay, but what if,
in the spirit of inclusion,
I tell you
"I love you" in sign language?
Oh, I love you too, Dad.
[Peter]
But this never happened
because no one resuscitated me.
I did wake up eventually,
but now I need help
feeding and bathing myself.
I spend most of my days
getting walked around
by a nurse who talks to
her sister on her phone.
[nurse]
Whoa, hold up.
Mom gave you the necklace?
[Peter]
That's her now.
♪ ♪
Well, Meg, I gotta say,
I'm proud of you for going to
that water park each day
and working a job that you love.
Oh, I quit that place.
-What?
-Yeah, the weather turned
two degrees cooler
than I like, so I just bailed.
That's the girl I raised.
Yay, our generation
folds at nothing.
And, Stewie, I'm sorry our
coffee house didn't work out.
I wonder how Principal
Shepherd's doing with it.
Eh, I hear he's going with
a "teachers' lounge" theme.
Your entire pastry case
is just Tupperware with people's
names written in Sharpie.
Don't forget this sad box of
donuts cut into quarters.
Everyone, let's all
talk about things
that parents have
told us in confidence.
[announcer] It's kind of like
Abbott Elementary,
which is amazing. Amazing!
You gotta watch it.
Oh, my God!